Oh, okay.
好的。
Where are we now?
我们现在在哪里？
Got the VRI for our\Ndeaf patient in Central 12.
我们在中央 12 号房间为聋人患者启动了视频远程口译服务。
Still waiting on Pedes\Nfor Baby Jane Doe.
还在等儿科医生来看 Baby Jane Doe。
Central 6 is sitting pretty\Nwith his insulin drip.
中央 6 号房间的患者胰岛素输液进行得很顺利。
And the Westbridge\Ndiversions are
而韦斯特布里奇的改道车辆
kindly waiting\Ntheir turn to sit
正在我们美丽的大厅里
for hours in our lovely halls.
耐心地等待他们的轮次坐上几个小时。
You are some kind of savant.
你是某种天才。
Worthy of a raise?
值得加薪吗？
Just more of my love.
只是我更多的爱。
I got enough of that.
我已经受够了。
I have a sexual\Nassault victim in triage.
我在分诊室有一名性攻击受害者。
I called PAAR,\Nso an advocate is on the way.
我打电话给了 PAAR，所以一名倡导者正在赶来。
Okay. We'll take care of it.
好的。我们会处理好的。
Uh, Dr. McKay, what's going on\Nwith your patient in Central 9?
呃，麦凯医生，中央 9 号病房你的患者怎么样了？
Isn't she good to go?
她不是可以出院了吗？
Oh, she was, but she decided
哦，她本来是可以的，但她改主意了
she wanted to stay\Nin the hospital now
她现在想留在医院
because she's in too much pain.
因为她疼痛太厉害了。
In our loud\Nand overcrowded ED
在我们嘈杂拥挤的急诊科
with more Westbridge cases\Narriving every moment?
每时每刻都有更多韦斯特布里奇的病例到来？
She would be\Nmore comfortable at home.
她在家会更舒适。
The debrief was lovely.
事后总结很愉快。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Would you mind helping Dana\Nwith a sexual assault victim
你能帮 Dana 处理一个性侵犯受害者吗
- who just came in?\N- Of course. Sure.
- 刚刚来的？ - 当然，没问题。
Why don't you and I go\Nsee if we can't convince
你和我一起去看看能不能说服
- your patient to leave?\N- All right.
- 你的病人离开？ - 好的。
I need to take care of a sexual\Nassault victim in triage.
我需要在分诊处照顾一个性侵犯受害者。
One of you needs\Nto hold down the fort.
你们中有人需要坚守阵地。
We can call for a SANE.\NOn a holiday? Could be hours.
我们可以叫一个性侵犯审查员。在假日？可能要等几个小时。
We're not gonna make\Nthis patient wait.
我们不能让这个患者等待。
And since I'm the only\NSANE on staff--
既然我是员工中唯一的性侵犯审查员——
Princess will cover.
公主会顶替。
Hey! Hey!
嘿！嘿！
You two better not be\Nteaching her any bad habits.
你们两个最好别教她坏习惯。
- Come on. You ready, Doc?\N- Sure.
- 来吧。你准备好了吗，医生？- 当然。
A SANE is a Sexual Assault\NNurse Examiner.
SANE 是性侵犯护士检查员。
We do forensic exams,\Ncollect evidence,
我们进行法医检查，收集证据，
and hand it over to the police\Nif a report is made.
如果有报告提交，就将其交给警方。
We also provide\Nresources, support,
我们还提供资源、支持，
- sometimes even testimony.\N- You go to court?
- 有时甚至提供证词。- 你要上法庭吗？
SANEs are very valuable in\Na hospital, especially an ED.
性侵犯护士检查员在医院中非常有价值，尤其是在急诊科。
More nurses should\Ntrain for it.
更多护士应该接受这方面的培训。
That's a not so subtle hint.
这是个不太含蓄的暗示。
Looks like this is\Nthe new hot spot, huh?
看起来这里是新的热门地点，是吧？
And only getting hotter.
而且越来越热了。
Any word on what's\Ngoing on with Westbridge?
有什么关于韦斯特布里奇的消息吗？
I got 20 on lantern flies.
我赌 20 块钱是灯蛾。
Nope, nothing.
不，什么都没有。
These patient passports have\Nan interesting alternative use.
这些患者护照有一个有趣的替代用途。
Where's the sexual\Nassault victim?
性侵犯受害者在哪里？
She's in Triage, Chair 2.
她在分诊区，椅子 2 号。
Thanks, Lupe.
谢谢你，卢佩。
Here's her intake.
这是她的初诊记录。
Got it.
明白了。
Hi, Ms. Miller.
你好，米勒女士。
I'm Dana.
我是达娜。
How are you doing?
你好吗？
- I've been better.\N- Yeah.
- 我见过更好的情况。- 是的。
You're in a safe place now.
你现在在一个安全的地方。
I'm the charge nurse in the ED
我是急诊科的护士长
and a sexual assault\Nnurse examiner.
也是性侵犯护理检查员。
This is Emma,\Nwho will be assisting.
这是艾玛，她会协助我们。
And I'm Dr. Al-Hashimi.
我是哈希米医生。
I'll be checking you\Nfor any injuries
我会检查你是否有任何需要立即处理的伤害。
that need immediate attention.
你可以叫我伊拉娜。
You can just call me Ilana.
我没有任何伤害。
I don't have any injuries.
Okay, that's good.
好的，很好。
We're gonna get\Na room ready for you.
我们会为你准备一个房间。
Meanwhile, Dr. Al-Hashimi is\Ngonna ask you a few questions.
同时，哈希米医生会问你几个问题。
How long is this gonna take?
这要花多长时间？
I can't promise\Nan exact time,
我无法保证具体的时间。
but we'll try to be\Nas fast as you need.
但我们会尽快为你服务。
- Thank you.\N- Yeah.
- 谢谢。- 好的。
Okay, Ilana, do you take any\Nprescription medications?
好的，伊拉娜，你服用任何处方药吗？
Just Synthroid,\None tab a day.
只有合成代谢激素，每天一片。
Okay, and any allergies\Nto medications?
好的，你对药物有过敏吗？
- No. No.\N- Okay.
- 不。不。- 好的。
Dana will come get you\Nwhen the room is ready,
房间准备好后，Dana 会来接你。
and I'll be back\Nto finish your exam.
我会回来给你做完检查。
Come find me\Nwhen she's in a gown.
她换上病号服后来找我。
Will do.
没问题。
We're gonna use Triage Exam\NRooms 1 and 2 for this.
我们将使用分诊考试室 1 和 2 来进行。
It's the most private space\Nwe have away from the ED.
这是我们远离急诊科最私密的空间。
All right, this can be a lot.
好的，这可能会很复杂。
You up for it?
你准备好了吗？
Yeah.
好的。
Yes. I'm good.
好的。我没问题。
Let me know if\Nyou need to step out.
如果你需要出去，告诉我一声。
Yes.
好的。
Dr. Ellis.
埃利斯医生。
- Oh, no.\N- Oh, yes.
- 哦，不。- 哦，是的。
Need the room.
需要用这个房间。
Find another place\Nto lay your head.
找个别的地方睡觉去。
Not even\Na 20-minute power nap?
连 20 分钟的小睡都不行？
You know, my double is at 1:30.\NI'm--
你知道，我的双人房在 1 点 30 分。我——
Nope, we're getting\NWestbridge diversions.
不行，我们要处理韦斯特布里奇的改道问题。
And chairs is insane.
椅子多得疯了。
- Did you see out there?\N- No.
- 你看到外面了吗？- 没有。
I do not come in\Nthrough that mess.
我不会穿过那堆乱七八糟的东西进去。
Okay.
好的。
Yeah.
People sleep in here?
人们在这里睡觉？
Yeah, the night shift docs\Njust need rest,
是的，夜班医生就是需要休息，
especially if they have to\Ncome in during the day.
特别是如果他们白天还要来。
But today, we can't\Nwaste the space.
但今天，我们不能浪费床位。
I need you to get me a stool on\Nwheels and Esme for a turnover.
我需要你给我拿一个带轮子的凳子，还有埃斯梅来交接班。
So you're having a headache\Nand abdominal pain?
所以你是头痛和腹痛？
Yeah, that's right.
是的，没错。
Okay, and which would\Nyou say is worse?
好的，那你说哪个更糟？
My headache was terrible\Nlast week...
我上周的头痛很厉害...
But now--
但现在--
Hey, you're--\Nyou're breaking up.
嘿，你--你的信号断了。
Can you run that back again?
你能再重复一遍吗？
Sure.
当然可以。
My headache was terrible\Nlast week...
我上周的头痛很厉害...
But now my abdominal pain--
但现在我的腹痛--
Oh, my God.
天哪。
Come on, you piece of--
来吧，你这个——
fuck.
混蛋。
Um--
嗯——
I'll--I'll be right back.
我——我马上回来。
Sorry.
抱歉。
Um, Dr. Al-Hashimi?
嗯，Al-Hashimi 医生？
Jackson's parents are here.
Jackson 的父母来了。
Okay. I'll take that.
好的。我接手了。
Um, Mr. and Mrs. Davis,\Nthis is one of my attendings,
嗯，Davis 先生和 Davis 太太，这是我的一位主治医生，
- Dr. Al-Hashimi.\N- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Al-Hashimi 医生。- 你好。很高兴认识你。
- Demi.\N- Charles.
- 德米。- 查尔斯。
What the hell's going on?
到底发生了什么？
He's barely conscious.
他几乎没有意识。
Jackson's just a little tired\Ndue to the sedative
杰克逊只是因为镇静剂有点累
- he was given.\N- You sedated him?
- 你给他用了镇静剂？- 他被注射了镇静剂。
Oh, your son was brought in\Nextremely agitated.
哦，你儿子被送进来时非常躁动。
You'd be, too,\Nif you were tased.
如果你被电击枪电过，你也会这样。
And why the fuck\Ndid they do that?
他们为什么要这样做？
This is bullshit.\NWe're taking him home.
这太荒唐了。我们要把他带回家。
Why don't we step out\Nfor a second?
我们出去谈一下好吗？
Right now, Jackson is on\Nan involuntary psych hold.
杰克逊现在被强制进行精神卫生观察。
What?\NThat's not necessary.
什么？这没必要。
He just needs some rest.
他只是需要休息。
He's been studying\Nfor the bar exam.
他一直在为律师资格考试复习。
We can watch him at home.
我们可以在家照看他。
So far, all of his tests\Nlook good,
到目前为止，他的所有检查结果都很好，
but Jackson has\Nreported hearing voices.
但杰克逊报告说听到了声音。
This could be serious.
这可能很严重。
Dr. Jefferson will come back\Nand speak with you.
杰斐逊医生会回来和你谈话。
He can explain more of what\Nmay be going on with Jackson.
他可以更详细地解释杰克逊可能发生了什么。
And who is Dr. Jefferson?
杰斐逊医生是谁？
He's from Psychiatry,\Nand he's excellent.
他来自精神病学科，非常出色。
He can explain next steps and\Nanswer all of your questions.
他可以解释后续步骤并回答你们的所有问题。
Javadi, why don't you take\Nthe Davises to the family room?
贾瓦迪，你能带戴维斯一家去家庭房吗？
- Sure.\N- Excuse me.
- 好的。- 对不起。
It's just this way.
就是这样。
You have reached the\NPittsburgh Neuroscience Group.
您已拨通匹兹堡神经科学集团。
If this is\Na medical emergency,
如果这是医疗紧急情况，
please hang up and dial 911.
请挂断电话并拨打 911。
For our address and\Noffice hours, press 1.
如需了解我们的地址和办公时间，请按 1。
To refill a prescription,\Npress 2.
要续配处方，请按 2。
To leave a message for\Nthe doctor on call--
要给值班医生留言--
Hi, this is\NDr. Baran al-Hashimi.
你好，我是巴兰·哈希米医生。
I'm a patient\Nof Dr. Fairgraves.
我是费尔格雷夫斯医生的患者。
I need to speak to him\Nif he's on call.
如果他值班，我需要和他谈话。
If he's not, I'll take his\Nnext available appointment.
如果他没有，我会预约他下一个可用的时间。
And please call me\Nif he has a cancellation.
如果他有取消的预约，请打电话给我。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Like I said, you're more than\Nwelcome to stay down here
就像我说的，欢迎你在这里等待
until an inpatient bed\Nopens up upstairs.
直到楼上有床位空出来。
But that can take a while,\Nsometimes days,
但那可能需要一段时间，有时要几天，
even longer.
会更长。
It's gonna be\Nreally noisy here,
这里会非常吵闹，
and you won't get any rest.
你无法得到任何休息。
At home, you'll be\Nsurrounded by your family
在家里，你会被家人包围
and be more comfortable.
会更加舒适。
It's your choice, Roxie.
这是你的选择，罗克西。
It's not that\NI don't wanna go home, but--
不是我不想回家，而是——
- Hi, Mom.\N- Mom.
- 嗨，妈妈。- 妈妈。
Lena texted me to come back.\NI figured I'd bring the boys.
莱娜给我发短信让我回来。我想我会把孩子们也带回去。
What's going on?\NIs everything okay?
发生什么事了？一切都好吗？
Robby, police officer,\Nincoming trauma.
罗比，警察，即将到达的创伤患者。
Coming.
来了。
I'll be right back.
我马上回来。
We'll give you\Na chance to talk.
我们会给你机会说话。
Okay, why don't you\Nhave a seat?
好的，你为什么不坐下呢？
Do you need anything\Nbefore we begin?
开始前你需要什么吗？
You're in control now, Ilana.
现在由你掌控，伊拉娜。
We're here to help\Nand support you.
我们在这里帮助和支持你。
Once I open this kit,\NI cannot leave the room.
一旦我打开这个工具包，我就不能离开这个房间。
But if you need a break\Nor some air, just let us know.
但如果你需要休息或透透气，就告诉我们。
Okay? Emma can go\Nwith you if you like.
好吧？如果你愿意，艾玛可以和你一起去。
An advocate from\NPittsburgh Action Against Rape
来自匹兹堡反强奸行动组织的倡导者
has been called,\Nand they should arrive soon.
已经被召来了，他们应该很快就会到达。
- Can we start?\N- Sure.
- 我们可以开始吗？- 当然可以。
I'm gonna put my face shield on
我要戴上面罩
so I don't\Ncontaminate anything.
所以我不会污染任何东西。
Emma has already done the same.
艾玛已经做过同样的事情了。
Now, in order for the doctor\Nto do her exam,
现在，为了让医生进行她的检查，
I need you in a gown,
我需要你穿上手术服，
but I need to collect\Nyour clothing first.
但我需要先收集你的衣服。
Is that okay?
可以吗？
I'm gonna need you to undress\Non top of these pads.
我需要你在这些垫子上脱衣服。
Put each item of clothing\Non the pads, okay?
把每件衣服都放在垫子上，好吗？
Then we'll package each piece\Nin a separate bag.
然后我们会把每一件都单独装在一个袋子里。
We'll get you new clothes.
我们会给你买新衣服。
- Don't worry.\N- All right.
- 别担心。- 好的。
Emma's gonna be\Nbehind this curtain,
艾玛会在这个窗帘后面，
and I'll be in here with you.
我会在这里和你在一起。
And take off your shoes first.
先脱掉你的鞋。
When you're done,\NI want you to put on your gown
完成后，我要你穿上你的病号服
open in the back.
后面开口。
What if the mom\Ndoesn't wanna leave?
如果妈妈不想离开怎么办？
Well, then she's gonna\Nhave to put up with us.
好吧，那她就得忍受我们了。
I can't imagine--her boys.
我无法想象——她的孩子们。
Oh, don't go there.
哦，别往那方面想。
I'm gonna see if\NI can grease the wheels,
我会试试能否加快进度，
get her a room upstairs soon.
尽快给她安排楼上的房间。
Good luck.\NWhat was that?
祝你好运。那是什么？
Battle plan\Nfor our hall space.
我们大厅空间的作战计划。
It's filling up fast.
它填满得很快。
Police officer should\Nbe here any minute.
警察应该马上就到。
Yeah, well, as soon\Nas you can, please,
好的，请尽快，
I need you to fix the VRI.
我需要你修理 VRI。
All right. Thanks.
好的。谢谢。
Santos, I need you\Nto pick up some more
桑托斯，我需要你再拿一些
- of these Westbridge diversions.\N- Sure.
- 这些韦斯特布里奇的转移病人。- 好的。
You want my firstborn too?
你还想要我的长子吗？
Maybe.\NWill they know how to suture?
也许吧。他们会缝合吗？
Intubated neck wound,\Nsats not great.
颈部插管伤口，血氧饱和度不理想。
We were diverted here.\NIs there a trauma room open?
我们被转移到这里。有创伤室空着吗？
- Trauma 1!\N- What's the story?
- 创伤 1 号！- 情况怎样？
My buddy, Officer Hiro,\Nhigh-velocity GSW.
我的搭档，警官 Hiro，高速枪伤。
He's getting harder to bag.
他越来越难进行人工呼吸了。
Warehouse robbery\Ngone sideways.
仓库抢劫出了问题。
One, two, three.
一、二、三。
You guys wait here.
你们在这里等着。
We'll take care of him,\NI promise.
我们会处理他，我保证。
I thought you left us\Nalready for the open road?
我以为你已经为了开阔的道路离开我们了？
And miss seeing you\Nin uniform?
我怎么能错过看你穿制服的样子呢？
You should see me\Nas a flight attendant.
你应该看看我穿空乘制服的样子。
- Did you do this intubation?\N- Under active fire, yeah.
- 你做的这个插管？- 是的，在枪林弹雨中。
Are you serious?
你是认真的吗？
I go in with the team\Nin case there's an injury.
我和队伍一起进去，以防有人受伤。
That's badass.
太酷了。
Dr. Santos, let's make sure\Nthese lungs are up.
桑托斯医生，我们确保这些肺部功能正常。
- Could you see the cords?\N- Yeah, there was a great view,
- 你能看到声带吗？- 是的，视野很清楚，
but it was hard to pass\Nafter I cleared them.
但我清理后很难通过。
Yeah, sats down to 85.
是的，血氧饱和度降到 85。
Dr. Santos, what could\Ncause respiratory failure
桑托斯医生，什么可能导致插管患者呼吸衰竭
in an intubated patient?
在插管患者中？
There are a lot\Nof possibilities.
有很多可能性。
Think DOPE.
想想 DOPE。
Displacement, Obstruction,\NPneumothorax,
移位、阻塞、气胸、
Equipment failure.
装备故障。
Good lung sliding, no pneumo.
肺滑动良好，无气胸。
It is displacement.
这是移位。
Okay, that is\Na transected trachea.
好的，这是气管断裂。
Pulling out.
正在拔出。
Bag.
袋子。
But if you intubate again,\Nwon't it just come straight
但如果你再插管，它不会直接从伤口出来吗？
- out the wound?\N- Yep, exactly.
- 是的，完全正确。
So we're gonna\Nneed another plan.
所以我们需要另想办法。
Okay. Sats down to 83.
好的。血氧饱和度降到 83。
Yeah, he's not\Nmoving any air.
是的，他没有呼吸。
Okay, I need a neonatal mask.
好的，我需要一个新生儿面罩。
- Neonatal?\N- Yep.
- 新生儿？- 是的。
I'm just going to finish\Nmy initial exam.
我只是要完成我的初步检查。
Let me know if you\Nfeel any pain, okay?
如果你感到任何疼痛，请告诉我，好吗？
My legs are fine.
我的腿没问题。
All looks good.
一切看起来都很好。
No need for X-rays\Nor advanced imaging.
不需要拍 X 光片或进行高级影像检查。
Got it.
明白了。
- Two areas of ecchymosis...\N- That means bruising.
- 两处淤血... - 那是指瘀伤。
Over the shoulders\Nbilaterally.
双侧肩膀上方。
- I'll document with photos.\N- Okay.
- 我会用照片记录。- 好的。
Dana will finish up her work,\Nand I will be in the ER
Dana 会完成她的工作，我会在急诊室
if you have any questions.
如果你有任何问题。
You're in great hands.
你在很好的照顾下。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
All right, Ilana.
好的，Ilana。
I read your intake.
我看过你的初诊表了。
Why don't you give me\Nyour description
你能给我讲一下
of exactly what happened?
具体发生了什么吗？
I was at\Na 4th of July barbecue
我当时在一个独立日烧烤聚会上
with a bunch of friends.
和一群朋友在一起。
I helped set up.
我帮着设置的。
Where does it hurt?
哪里疼？
Like here,\Nunder my belly button.
就在这儿，肚脐下面。
Okay, do you have any fever,\Nvomiting, diarrhea?
好的，你有发烧、呕吐或腹泻吗？
Oh, no.\NIt's--it's just a stomachache.
哦，没有。就是——就是胃疼。
Okay, well, still, go see\Nthe nurse and have her call me.
好吧，不过，还是去看看护士，让她给我打电话。
Okay.
好的。
But I'm still having\Nice cream tonight.
但我今晚还是要吃冰淇淋。
Why don't you see\Nhow you feel later?
你为什么不等等看自己感觉怎么样？
It--it's not bad.\NYou don't have to get so sad.
这——这不是什么大问题。你不必这么难过。
I'm not sad.\NI'm--I'm good.
我不难过。我——我很好。
Your face doesn't look good.
你的脸色看起来不太好。
Oh.
哦。
Well, you still wanna watch\Nthe fireworks tonight?
你今晚还想看烟火吗？
I have our headphones--
我有我们的耳机——
- I'm not being rude.\N- Sorry, Becca. I gotta go.
- 我不是在无礼。- 对不起，贝卡。我得走了。
Elliot Green, 17, syncopal\Nepisode at football practice.
埃利奥特·格林，17 岁，在足球训练中晕厥发作。
Look, I just got dizzy, okay?
听着，我只是有点头晕，好吗？
It's hell week.\NI need to get back.
这是地狱周。我得回去。
Yeah, okay, tough guy.
好吧，硬汉。
A and O, systolic of 95, tachy\Nat 122, no meds, no allergies.
意识清醒，收缩压 95，心率 122，无用药史，无过敏史。
How long were you\Nat practice?
你在训练中待了多久？
I started at 9:00,\Nso, like, four hours.
我 9 点开始的，所以大概四个小时。
Four hours in this heat\Nwith all that gear?
在这种炎热中穿着全套装备四个小时？
No pain, no game.
没有痛苦，就没有游戏。
God, I'm hungry.
天哪，我饿了。
Hey. When's our break?\NThere's no breaks down here.
嘿。我们什么时候休息？这里没有休息时间。
Always make sure you pack\Na protein bar, something quick.
一定要记得带上蛋白棒，什么快速的东西都行。
Ogilvie, Joy,\Njump in on this.
奥吉尔维，乔伊，你们加入讨论一下。
Syncope at football practice.
足球训练中晕倒。
No, I just--\NI just needed to hydrate.
不，我只是——我只是需要补充水分。
Possible heatstroke?
可能是中暑？
Well, with heatstroke,\Nyou would have
好吧，中暑的话，你会有
an altered mental status.
精神状态改变。
And they're usually dry,\Nnot sweaty.
他们通常是干燥的，不会出汗。
Mortality is 50%,\Nespecially in the elderly.
死亡率为 50%，特别是在老年人中。
In extreme heat like this...
在这样的极端高温下...
Langdon, can you cover this?
兰登，你能处理这个吗？
- No problem.\N- Mr. Diaz. Orlando.
- 没问题。- 迪亚兹先生。奥兰多。
Orlando, where are you going?
奥兰多，你要去哪里？
- Home. Can you take these out?\N- Uh, no.
- 回家。你能把这些拿出去吗？- 呃，不行。
It takes 48 hours for you\Nto get out of DKA.
你需要 48 小时才能摆脱糖尿病酮症酸中毒。
Your blood is still\Nfull of acid.
你的血液中仍然充满了酸。
Look, I can't add\Nthousands of dollars
听着，我不能再加上数千美元
to the 100 grand I already owe.
到我已经欠的 10 万美元上。
I'm--I'm sorry.\N100 grand?
我——我很抱歉。10 万美元？
In medical debt.\NMy wife doesn't even know.
医疗债务。我的妻子甚至不知道。
I'll never be able\Nto pay it off as it is.
我根本无法还清。
Where are your wife\Nand daughter?
你的妻子和女儿在哪里？
Maybe we can all talk.
也许我们可以一起谈谈。
I told them to go back\Nto work a couple hours ago.
我几小时前告诉他们回去工作了。
But the hospital is\Ngiving you a big discount.
但医院给你一个很大的折扣。
And, Mr. Diaz,\NI know it's not ideal,
而且，迪亚兹先生，我知道这不是理想的情况，
but can you stay\Nfor at least 12 hours?
但你能至少待 12 个小时吗？
It would get you out\Nof the danger zone.
这样你就能脱离危险区域。
No. I really can't.
不行。我真的不能。
Every minute I stay is a meal,\Nshoes, school supplies.
我待的每一分钟都是一顿饭、一双鞋、学用品的钱。
Plus, I have a second job\NI have to get to by 4:00.
而且，我还有第二份工作要在下午 4 点前赶到。
- You need fluids!\N- I drink plenty of water.
- 你需要补充液体！- 我喝了很多水。
And potassium and insulin.\NOkay, how about this?
还有钾和胰岛素。好吧，这样怎么样？
You stay and I'll get together\Neverything you'll need at home.
你留下来，我会把你在家需要的一切都准备好。
Also, a referral to Northside\NChristian Health Center.
另外，还有转诊到北区基督教健康中心。
Come on.\NYou don't work until 4:00.
来吧。你到 4 点才上班。
It'll keep you from passing out\Non the job again--
这样你就不会再在工作中昏迷了——
or worse.
或者更糟的情况。
Okay, I guess.
好吧，我想可以。
Great.
太好了。
Thank you. Please.
谢谢你。拜托了。
Sats up to 98.
血氧饱和度达到 98。
- Neonatal mask is working.\N- Santos, finish the FAST.
- 新生儿面罩在工作。- 桑托斯，完成 FAST 检查。
What--what are\Nyou injecting?
你在注射什么？
Lido with epi.
利多卡因加肾上腺素。
It'll clamp off\Nany little bleeders.
它会止住任何小的出血点。
We need some skin hooks.\N4 Shiley?
我们需要一些皮肤钩。4 个 Shiley 的？
Mm, I don't like\Nthe curve of a Shiley.
嗯，我不喜欢 Shiley 的弧度。
I didn't know\Nyou were so picky.
我不知道你这么挑剔。
Santos, take a break.
Santos，休息一下。
Help me cut down a 6-0 ET tube.
帮我剪短一根 6-0 ET 导管。
What is going on here?
这里发生了什么？
You have a field medic\Nassisting you?
你有一名野战医疗兵在协助你？
Dr. Abbot is an attending,
Abbott 医生是主治医生，
and he's also a SWAT physician.
他也是特警队的内科医生。
My buddy Hiro here\Nis in bad need of an airway.
我的伙伴 Hiro 这里急需建立气道。
- Cut it right here.\N- We can do this.
- 就在这里剪。- 我们可以做到。
No, no, I got it.
不，不，我来。
You must be Gloria's new hire.
你一定是格洛丽亚新招的员工。
Yes. Dr. Al-Hashimi.
是的。哈希米博士。
Well, I'd shake your hand,\Nbut my tube is ready.
好吧，我想和你握手，但我的导管已经准备好了。
And if I could find\Nand secure the distal trachea,
如果我能找到并固定远端气管，
we have a shot at this.
我们就有机会了。
Okay, keeping\Nan eye on the sats.
好的，密切关注血氧饱和度。
Slow is smooth.\NSmooth is fast.
慢即是稳。稳即是快。
You know, you can call me\Njust to say hi sometimes.
你知道，有时候你可以打电话给我，只是为了打个招呼。
What's up now?
现在怎么样？
GSW with tracheal\Ntransection.
枪伤伴气管断裂。
Very retracted,\Nbut I think I can get it.
收缩很明显，但我认为我能处理。
Both lungs are up?
两个肺都上来了？
- Sats down to 91.\N- Scanning the belly now.
- 血氧饱和度降到 91。- 现在在扫描腹部。
Okay.
好的。
I got it. I got it.
我明白了。我明白了。
Gently, gently,\Nor we're gonna lose it.
轻一点，轻一点，否则我们会失去它。
Down to 89.
降到 89。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
I'm in. Balloon up.
我进去了。充气球。
End tidal,\Nexcellent wave form.
呼气末，波形很好。
Good breath sounds.
呼吸音良好。
I'll sew the tracheal\Nto the skin, 2-0 silk.
我会用 2-0 丝线将气管缝到皮肤上。
- Sats are coming up.\N- Whoo.
- 血氧饱和度在上升。- 哇。
Not bad, Abbot.
不错，艾博特。
Mm, while you were playing\Nwith that airway,
嗯，当你在处理那条气道的时候，
you missed a big bruise\Nin the left upper quadrant.
你错过了左上象限的一个大淤伤。
He was wearing body armor.
他穿着防具。
High-velocity projectile\Ndoesn't have
高速射弹没有
to penetrate to damage.
穿透造成损伤。
There's no fluid\Nin the suprasplenic space.
脾上间隙没有液体。
Let me look.
让我看看。
Okay, right there.
好的，就在那里。
Looks like a subcapsular\Nhematoma of his spleen.
看起来是他脾脏的被膜下血肿。
Must have been a big impact.
肯定造成了很大的冲击。
AR-15 muzzle velocity\Nis 3,000 feet per second.
AR-15 枪口速度是每秒 3,000 英尺。
CT angio of the neck ASAP,
立即进行颈部 CT 血管造影，
along with CT chest,\Nabdomen, pelvis.
以及胸部、腹部、骨盆 CT。
Yep, just as soon\Nas we secure this tube.
是的，我们一固定好这根导管就马上做。
- First liter's in.\N- Mucous membranes dry.
- 第一升液体已输入。- 粘膜干燥。
Pupils 4 millimeters\Nreactive.
瞳孔 4 毫米，有反应。
Did you get tackled today?
你今天被铲倒了吗？
No, just running drills.
没有，只是在做训练。
Any chest pain?\NPalpitations?
有胸痛吗？心悸？
No.
不行。
Hands off, please,\Nrunning the 12 lead.
请不要碰，正在做 12 导联心电图。
How are we looking?
情况怎么样？
Good. Healthy kid.
很好。孩子很健康。
No history, no trauma.
没有病史，没有外伤。
Differential for syncope\Nin an adolescent?
青少年晕厥的鉴别诊断？
Cardiac arrhythmia\Nfrom drugs...
药物引起的心律不齐...
- Hypovolemia, seizure...\N- Long QT, WPW...
- 低血容量、癫痫发作... - 长 QT 间期、WPW...
- Sepsis.\N- Or Brugada.
- 脓毒症。 - 或 Brugada 综合征。
Uh, Brugada is more\Ncommon in Asian males.
嗯，Brugada 综合征在亚洲男性中更常见。
But still\Nshould be considered.
但仍然应该考虑。
Long odds, though.
概率很低，不过。
Brugada prevalence is\N1 in 20,000 in North America,
布鲁加达综合征在北美的患病率为 1/20,000，
as high as 1 in 300 in Asia\Nand the Middle East.
在亚洲和中东地区高达 1/300。
And?
那又怎样？
First described in 1992,\Nhas a high incidence
首次在 1992 年被描述，在心脏结构正常的年轻患者中突然死亡的发生率很高
of sudden death among\Nyoung patients with otherwise
- 结构正常的心脏-- - 哎呀，哎呀，等等。
- structurally normal hearts--\N- Oof, oof, wait.
你刚才说"突然死亡"吗？
Did you just say\N"sudden death"?
体温是 102.5。
Temp is 102.5.
Sorry, our student doctors\Nare discussing
抱歉，我们的学生医生在讨论
a rare condition\Nyou don't have.
一种你没有的罕见病。
I--I just didn't\Ndrink enough water.
我——我只是没有喝足够的水。
I overheated.
我过热了。
Not my type, bud.
不是我的菜，伙计。
Other than standard labs,\Nwhat else to order?
除了标准检查外，还需要检查什么？
CK to rule out rhabdo.
肌酸激酶检查以排除横纹肌溶解症。
To make sure you don't have
确保你没有
any muscle breakdown\Nfrom the heat.
因高温导致的肌肉分解。
Let's set up a cooling room\Nfor Elliot here
我们为埃利奥特在这里设置一个降温室吧
and the other heat exhaustions\Nwe'll inevitably get today.
以及我们今天不可避免会遭遇的其他热衰竭。
Last photo.
最后一张照片。
Okay.
好的。
We'll take the SD card\Nand seal it
我们会取出 SD 卡并将其密封
in an evidence envelope\Nwith everything else.
放入证物信封，和其他物品一起。
Okay.
好的。
Next, Emma's gonna\Nturn off the light,
接下来，艾玛会关掉灯，
and I'll run a blue light\Nover your skin.
我会用蓝光照射你的皮肤。
Anything glows, I'll swab it\Nwith a wet, then dry Q-tip.
如果有任何地方发光，我会用湿的棉签擦拭，然后用干棉签擦干。
Is that okay?
可以吗？
Yeah, sure.
好的，没问题。
All right.
好的。
Take off your gown\Non the left side
把你左边的衣服脱掉
and turn a little bit\Ntowards me, just to the left.
稍微转向我这边，向左一点。
There.
好的。
Something on the left wrist.
左腕上有什么东西。
Swab.
擦拭。
Sorry.
抱歉。
Don't be.
别紧张。
- It's just cold.\N- Yeah.
- 只是冷。- 是的。
Almost done.
快完成了。
- Thanks, Antoine.\N- No problem.
- 谢谢你，安托万。- 没问题。
Keep your head down out there.
在外面保持低调。
What's the story?
怎么回事？
Neck angio is negative,\Nmissed the carotids.
颈部血管造影阴性，漏掉了颈动脉。
- He's lucky.\N- What about the belly?
- 他很幸运。- 腹部怎么样？
Small splenic injury,\Nno free fluid in the abdomen.
脾脏轻微损伤，腹腔内无游离液体。
- That should heal on its own.\N- What's the plan?
- 那应该会自行愈合。- 计划是什么？
Head and Neck will have\Nan OR ready
头颈外科会准备好手术室
with thoracic standing by.
胸外科待命。
How soon can they take him?
他们什么时候能接收他？
We're a little backed up\Nwith Westbridge patients,
我们现在韦斯特布里奇的患者有点多，
but let's bring him up.
但让我们把他送上来。
I'll get him\Ntaken care of for you.
我会为你照顾好他。
Hey.
嘿。
You're gonna be okay, Hiro.\NWe're getting you to surgery.
你会没事的，希罗。我们要给你做手术。
I'll write\Nthe procedure note.
我来写手术记录。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
SWAT? Really?
特警队？真的吗？
I suck at golf.
我高尔夫球打得很烂。
You spend time\Nin the Middle East?
你在中东待过很长时间？
More than I would have liked.
比我想象的要长。
I worked in Kabul\Nwith Médecins Sans Frontières
我曾在喀布尔为无国界医生组织工作
and in 2020,\Nat the maternity hospital.
2020 年时在妇产医院。
I met the most incredible,\Nbravest doctors there.
我在那里遇见了最不可思议、最勇敢的医生们。
Dasht-e-Barchi.
巴尔奇沙漠。
Tragedy.
悲剧。
We should grab a beer sometime,\Nshare war stories.
我们应该找个时间喝啤酒，分享战争故事。
I'd like that.
我很乐意。
She seems cool.
她看起来不错。
Yep, maybe.
是的，也许吧。
I'm not gonna be around\Nlong enough to find out.
我不会在这里呆足够长的时间来找出答案。
Oh, there she is! Vic!
哦，她来了！维克！
Dad!
爸爸！
Victoria,\Nthis is Dr. Amy Joon.
维多利亚，这是艾米·琼医生。
Dr. Joon is the smartest\Nperson I know.
乔恩医生是我认识的最聪明的人。
Don't tell your mother.\NJust kidding.
别告诉你妈妈。开玩笑的。
But seriously, don't.
但说真的，别告诉。
- Hi.\N- Hello.
- 嗨。- 你好。
Are--are you here\Nto see a patient?
你——你是来看病人的吗？
No.\NWe're here to see you.
不是。我们是来见你的。
Dr. Joon is Chief\Nof Dermatology.
Joon 医生是皮肤科主任。
And Victoria's first\Nshift in the ER
Victoria 在急诊室的第一班
was on the day\Nof the PittFest shooting.
正好是 PittFest 枪击事件那天。
I heard all\Nthe incredible stories,
我听说了所有那些不可思议的故事，
including your own acts\Nof med student prowess.
包括你自己的医学生杰出表现。
Wow, med student prowess.
哇，医学生的杰出表现。
That's--\NI'm--I'm pretty sure
那是——我——我很确定
I was just trying\Nto stay out of the way.
我只是想不碍事。
Ah, she's modest,\Nlike her dad.
啊，她很谦虚，像她爸爸一样。
And her mother?
她的母亲呢？
Oh. Sorry.
哦。抱歉。
Dr. Joon.
朱恩医生。
Yep, coming.
是的，来了。
I'm doing a favor for someone\Nat the mayor's office
我在为市长办公室的某个人帮忙。
who needs Mohs surgery\Non a basal cell carcinoma.
需要对基底细胞癌进行莫氏手术的人。
And then I am grilling for 30.
然后我要为 30 个人烧烤。
- Oh, wow.\N- Happy 4th, all.
- 哇哦。- 祝大家 7 月 4 日快乐。
- Happy 4th.\N- Yeah.
- 祝 7 月 4 日快乐。- 是的。
- Thanks for coming down.\N- My pleasure.
- 感谢你来。- 我很荣幸。
- Let's grab a coffee sometime.\N- Absolutely. Yes.
- 咱们找个时间喝个咖啡吧。- 当然可以。好的。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
You know Mom really wants me\Nto go into surgery.
你知道妈妈真的想让我去做手术。
Ah, your mom wants me\Nto stop drinking
啊，你妈妈想让我戒酒
- and join a pickleball league.\N- Oh, that's the same.
- 还有加入一个皮克球联赛。- 哦，那是一样的。
- Yeah, well--\N- Exact same.
- 是啊，嗯-- - 完全一样。
I will risk an Achilles tear\Nbefore I give up scotch.
我宁愿冒着跟腱撕裂的风险也不会放弃威士忌。
Hey, I hope I didn't\Nembarrass you coming down here.
嘿，我希望我来这里没有让你尴尬。
No.
不行。
I'm just trying to present\Nyou with some options
我只是想给你提供一些选择
for your residency.
关于你的住院医生培训。
I--I really\Nappreciate it, Dad.
我——我真的很感谢你，爸爸。
I do.\NI just--
我愿意。我只是——
I'm still not sure.
我仍然不确定。
Well, either way,\Nyou'll do what's right.
好吧，无论如何，你会做正确的事。
You always do.
你总是这样。
- Proud of ya.\N- Okay.
- 为你感到骄傲。- 好的。
Dr. Javadi, you are\Na man of many talents.
贾瓦迪博士，你是一个多才多艺的人。
You don't know the half of it.
你根本不知道我有多厉害。
Your daughter has some
你的女儿有一些
high standards to live up to.
很高的标准要达到。
Oh, you don't know\Nthe half of it.
哦，你根本不知道我有多厉害。
Mr. and Mrs. Davis, this is\NDr. Jefferson from Psychiatry.
戴维斯先生和太太，我是精神科的杰斐逊医生。
Please call me Caleb.
请叫我凯莱布。
Can you tell us what's\Ngoing on with our son?
你们能告诉我们你们儿子怎么了吗？
All of his labs\Nand X-rays came back normal.
他的所有检查和 X 光片结果都正常。
Given his age\Nand his hearing voices,
考虑到他的年龄和他听到声音的情况，
do either of you have a family\Nhistory of mental illness?
你们中有人有精神疾病的家族史吗？
Not mine.
我没有。
My brother took his own life.
我哥哥自杀了。
Wait, what?
等等，什么？
Uncle Ken?
肯叔叔？
You said he drank\Nhimself to death.
你说他喝酒喝死了。
- Ma.\N- He did that too.
- 妈妈。- 他也确实这样做了。
Was he ever\Nformally diagnosed
他是否曾被正式诊断过
with a mental health issue?
患有心理健康问题？
No.
不行。
He was depressed,\Nhad mood swings.
他患有抑郁症，情绪波动很大。
- But he didn't wanna see anyone.\N- Oh, my God.
- 但他不想见任何人。- 天哪。
Okay, why am I just now\Nhearing about this?
好吧，我为什么现在才听说这件事？
- Jada, please.\N- Please what, Mom?
- 杰达，拜托。- 拜托什么，妈妈？
Why would you not\Ntell Jackson or me?
你为什么不告诉杰克逊或我？
I can't believe this.
我简直不敢相信。
- Jada.\N- Excuse me.
- 杰达。- 打扰一下。
Jada.
杰达。
What happens next?
接下来会怎样？
We keep your son here\Nfor the next three days
我们会让你的儿子在这里待三天
for observation and therapy.
进行观察和治疗。
And that will help us\Nto understand what is going on.
这样会帮助我们理解发生了什么。
Jada should really hear this.
杰达真的应该听听这个。
Let me see if I can find her,\Nbring her back.
让我看看我能不能找到她，把她带回来。
Okay.\NI'm gonna swab your mouth now.
好的。我现在要给你的嘴里取样。
My mouth?
我的嘴？
Two dry swabs along\Nthe inside of your cheek
用两根干棉签沿着你的脸颊内侧擦拭
and then along the gum line.
然后沿着牙龈线擦拭。
How you feeling?
你感觉怎么样？
I wish this day\Nnever happened.
我希望这一天从未发生过。
Would you like some medicine\Nto help you relax?
你想要一些药物来帮助你放松吗？
You've experienced\Na horrific trauma.
你经历过可怕的创伤。
You've been\Ndoing this a while?
你做这个有一段时间了？
Let's just say\NFlorence Nightingale
就说我和弗洛伦斯·南丁格尔
and I were roommates.
是室友吧。
Who?
谁？
I rest my case.
我的论证到此结束。
She was the founder\Nof modern nursing.
她是现代护理学的创始人。
Okay, you can have something\Nto eat or drink now.
好的，你现在可以吃点东西或喝点饮料了。
- I'm fine.\N- Are you sure?
- 我很好。- 你确定吗？
I'll just keep going.
我会继续坚持下去。
Okay.
好的。
We now have a heat exhaustion\Ntreatment area in North 5.
我们现在在北 5 区有了一个热衰竭治疗区。
Evaporated cooling.\NGreat plan.
蒸发冷却。很好的计划。
Yeah, it was\NDr. Langdon's idea.
是的，这是兰登医生的主意。
He figured we'd be seeing a lot\Nmore patients in this heat.
他认为在这种炎热的天气里我们会看到更多的患者。
He's right.
他说得对。
How are you feeling?
你感觉怎么样？
That's a loaded question.
这是个很难回答的问题。
It wasn't meant to be.
我没有那个意思。
You have a deposition\Nin a couple of hours?
你几小时后要去作证？
- Yes.\N- How are you feeling about it?
- 是的。- 你感觉怎么样？
Um, trying\Nto think positively
嗯，我在尽力往积极的方面想。
but feeling, um, less so.
但感觉上，嗯，没那么多。
This job's really important\Nto me and my sister.
这份工作对我和我妹妹来说真的很重要。
You know, I support both of us.
你知道，我支持我们两个。
It's gonna go great.
一切都会很顺利的。
Just tell them what happened.
就告诉他们发生了什么。
You're not at fault.\NYour job's not in jeopardy.
这不是你的错。你的工作不会有危险。
I mean, the lawyers\Nsaid that I could--
我是说，律师们说我可以——
The lawyers' job is to try\Nand shake your confidence.
律师的工作就是试图动摇你的信心。
So don't let them.\NYou're a very good doctor.
所以别让他们得逞。你是一位非常优秀的医生。
I have been training\Nresidents for years.
我已经培训住院医生多年了。
You are one of the very best.
你是最优秀的人之一。
I am?
我是吗？
No, we need\Nto stick to the plan.
不，我们需要坚持计划。
- I promise.\N- Look.
- 我保证。- 看。
Thanks.
谢谢。
She's not thinking\Nclearly, okay?
她现在思路不清楚，好吗？
It's gonna be great.
这会很棒的。
This is not what she wants.
这不是她想要的。
Then I'm taking her home.\NThat's it.
那我就带她回家。就这样。
We have to honor\Nyour wife's wishes.
我们必须尊重你妻子的意愿。
Even if she's\Nloaded up on morphine
即使她注射了大量吗啡
- and can't think straight?\N- Especially then.
- 神志不清？ - 尤其是那时候。
Hello.
你好。
Paul Hamler, this is\Nmy attending, Dr. Robinavitch.
我是保罗·哈姆勒，这是我的主治医生罗宾诺维奇医生。
- Hi.\N- Hi.
- 你好。 - 你好。
Uh, my wife is not\Nthinking clearly.
嗯，我妻子思路不清。
What is it that\Nshe's asking for?
她要求什么？
Said she wants to stay here.
她说她想留在这里。
Why don't we all\Ngo in and talk?
我们为什么不都进去谈谈？
Brian Jenkins is\Nallowed to hunt with a .22
布莱恩·詹金斯被允许用.22 口径枪狩猎。
on his grandpa's farm.
在他爷爷的农场上。
Sounds like an accident\Njust waiting to happen.
听起来像是一场随时都会发生的事故。
Mm-hmm.\NAnd you're not Brian Jenkins.
嗯。而且你不是布莱恩·詹金斯。
How are we doing\Nin here, Roxie?
我们在这里进展如何，罗克西？
Been better.
还可以。
Rumor has it\Nyou're still interested
听说你还有兴趣
in booking a room with us?
在我们这儿订个房间？
I don't wanna\Ngo back home yet.
我还不想回家。
It's all set up, Rox.
一切都安排好了，罗克丝。
You're gonna be\Nmore comfortable at home.
你在家会更舒服。
Paul, I changed my mind.
保罗，我改主意了。
It is our home.
这是我们的家。
I don't--
我不——
I don't want you\Nliving with my ghost.
我不想让你和我的幽灵一起生活。
I will happily\Nlive with your ghost.
我很乐意和你的幽灵一起生活。
Can we just all stop\Ntalking about ghosts, please?
我们能都别再谈论鬼魂了吗？拜托了。
Yes. I'm sorry.
好的。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry, sweetie.\NYou're right.
我很抱歉，亲爱的。你说得对。
Got trauma flying in.\NETA, five minutes.
有创伤患者即将到达。预计到达时间，五分钟。
Okay.\NUm, I'm very sorry.
好的。嗯，我非常抱歉。
I will be right back.
我马上回来。
Excuse me.
对不起。
It's a boating accident,\Nswimmer versus propeller.
这是一起划船事故，游泳者与螺旋桨相撞。
Ouch.
哎哟。
- What body parts involved?\N- They didn't say.
- 涉及身体的哪些部位？- 他们没有说。
- How old?\N- Nope.
- 多大了？- 没有。
Anything?
有什么线索吗？
All I got was\Nboating accident,
我只知道是一起划船事故，
- swimmer versus propeller.\N- Propeller. Got it.
- 游泳者对上螺旋桨。- 螺旋桨。明白了。
Picked a hell of a day\Nto come back, huh?
选了个该死的日子回来，嗯？
How's Jake?
杰克怎么样？
He's good.
他很好。
He's better. He's coping.
他更好了。他在应对得很好。
He's gonna be\Na senior this fall.
他今年秋天就要成为大四学生了。
That's great.
那太好了。
That was a lot\Nfor him to go through.
他经历了很多。
A lot for all of us\Nto go through.
我们都经历了很多。
Yeah.
好的。
Okay, I'm just gonna say it!
好吧，我就直说了！
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉。
I betrayed your trust.
我背叛了你的信任。
I betrayed our patients' trust.
我背叛了我们患者的信任。
And I'm really fucking sorry.
我真的非常抱歉。
It'll never happen again,\NI swear.
我发誓这种事再也不会发生。
I'm really glad that you\Ngot the help that you need.
我真的很高兴你得到了你需要的帮助。
But I don't know if\NI want you working in my ER.
但我不确定是否想让你在我的急诊室工作。
Why'd you intubate him?
你为什么给他插管？
He was splinting\Nfrom the pain,
他因为疼痛而肌肉僵硬，
barely moving air\Nwith sats in the 80s.
气流流动很少，血氧饱和度只有 80 多。
How'd he get sliced up\Nin the propeller?
他怎么被螺旋桨割伤的？
He was in the Allegheny
他在阿勒格尼河里
trying to untangle\Na water ski tow line
试图解开水上滑雪拖绳
when his buddy\Nstarted the engine.
这时他的伙伴启动了引擎。
Drunk buddy, I assume?
我猜是醉酒的伙伴？
Well, it's 4th of July.\NYou tell me.
嗯，今天是 7 月 4 日。你自己判断吧。
Focus on the patient, please.
请专注于患者，谢谢。
Sofie, take over bagging.
索菲，你来负责装袋。
Okay. One, two, three.
好的。一、二、三。
Watch that buckle.
小心那个扣子。
- Do you need me in here?\N- Nope.
- 你需要我在这儿吗？- 不用。
We have a senior resident\Nand an attending.
我们有一位资深住院医生和一位主治医生。
Mel, can we start with a--
梅尔，我们能从——开始吗？
- An EFAST? Sure.\N- Yes, please.
- 做 EFAST 检查？当然可以。- 好的，谢谢。
Why?
为什么？
To check and make sure\Nthere's no pneumothorax.
检查并确保没有气胸。
Otherwise, it could\Nbecome a tension.
否则，可能会引发紧张局面。
Exactly. Oh, wow.
完全同意。哇。
- You want O-neg?\N- Not without a BP first.
- 你要 O 阴性血？ - 先量血压再说。
108/64, pulse is 102.
血压 108/64，脉搏 102。
- Sats are good.\N- Okay, let's have O-neg ready,
- 血氧饱和度很好。 - 好的，准备好 O 阴性血，
- but don't give it just yet.\N- Anything else?
- 但先别给。- 还有别的吗？
How about a hemocue?
血红蛋白仪怎么样？
Uh, yeah.\NYeah, yeah, of course.
嗯，好的。好的，好的，当然。
Next step is fingernails.
下一步是指甲。
We'll go under each nail,
我们会检查每个指甲下面，
first with the wet swab\Nand then with the dry one.
先用湿棉签，然后用干棉签。
Do you wanna take a break, hon?
你想休息一下吗，亲爱的？
No.
不行。
How much longer?
还要多久？
After these,\Nwe'll get to external...
这些之后，我们会进行外部采集...
And internal\Nvaginal collection.
以及内部阴道采集。
It's the advocate from PAAR.
这是来自 PAAR 的倡导者。
They've been doing this\Nlonger than I have.
他们从事这项工作的时间比我长。
They provide resources,\Nassistance, and support
他们提供资源、协助和支持
for sexual assault survivors.
给性暴力幸存者。
Hey.
嘿。
This will not define you, okay?
这不会定义你，好吗？
You don't have to talk to them,\Nbut I recommend you do.
你不必和他们交谈，但我建议你这样做。
They're available 24/7.
他们全天候 24 小时提供服务。
- Okay.\N- Okay.
- 好的。- 好的。
Hi.
嗨。
I'm Paulette Sanderson from\NPittsburgh Action Against Rape.
我是来自匹兹堡反强奸行动组织的保莱特·桑德森。
Hi, Paulette.\NI'm the SANE, Dana.
嗨，波莱特。我是 SANE 的达娜。
- And this is Ilana.\N- Hello.
- 这是伊拉娜。- 你好。
I'm sorry to meet you\Nunder these circumstances,
很遗憾在这样的情况下认识你，
but I and my organization\Nare here to help you navigate
但我和我的组织在这里帮助你应对
everything that comes next.
接下来发生的一切。
I brought you some clothes\Nand basic necessities.
我给你带了一些衣服和日用必需品。
I can even stay with you\Nthrough the rest
如果你愿意，我甚至可以陪你完成剩下的
of your examination\Nif you'd like.
检查。
I don't think\Nthat's necessary.
我认为没有必要。
- Okay.\N- That's fine.
- 好的。- 没问题。
Would it be okay if\NI asked you a few questions?
我能问你几个问题吗？
Sure.
当然可以。
Mm, our VRI isn't working.
嗯，我们的 VRI 坏了。
Video Relay Interpreter?
视频远程传译员？
Yeah, of course I rebooted it.
是的，当然我重启过了。
Wait, how are you gonna\Nfix it if you don't know
等等，你不知道的话怎么修呢
what the hell it is?
这到底是什么？
Yeah, okay.\NWhatever.
好吧，随便。
I wanna do a head\Nand belly scan on Harlow.
我想给哈洛做头部和腹部扫描。
Can you try telling her why?
你能试着告诉她原因吗？
What about the VRI?
VRI 呢？
It's DOA.
它已经死了。
I'm charting every\Nfree minute I get.
我在利用每一分钟空闲时间做图表。
I wasn't coming over\Nfor that.
我不是为了那个才过来的。
Good job in the Trauma earlier.
你之前在创伤科的表现不错。
What's this?
这是什么？
Daniel Scott, 32,
丹尼尔·斯科特，32 岁，
weak and dizzy\Nwhile washing his car.
洗车时感到虚弱和头晕。
Tachy at 106, BP 90/60.
心率 106 次/分，血压 90/60。
Temp's too high to register.
体温高到无法测量。
We have a cooling room\Nset up in North 5.
我们在北 5 区设置了一个降温室。
Okay, how are you\Nfeeling, Mr. Scott?
好的，斯科特先生，你感觉怎么样？
Thirsty.
口渴。
Let's see if\Nwe can't fix that.
让我们看看能否解决这个问题。
He's gonna need a core temp,\Na CMP--whoa.
他需要测核心体温、综合代谢面板——哇。
Oh, hey, we need\Na trauma room.
哦，嘿，我们需要一间创伤室。
- What's open?\N- 2.
- 什么开放了？- 2。
I'll grab the Ativan.
我去拿阿替唑仑。
- Any past medical history?\N- No.
- 有既往病史吗？- 没有。
Wife says he's healthy.\NNo meds, no allergies.
妻子说他很健康。没有用药，没有过敏。
He needs a core temp.
他需要测核心体温。
Ready to transfer.
准备转移。
Let's give 2 of Ativan.
给他用 2 单位的阿提万。
Don't want him seizing again.
不想让他再发作。
I gotta get back\Nto my patients.
我得回去看我的病人。
Okay.
好的。
One, two, three.
一、二、三。
Orders?
有什么医嘱吗？
Second IV with saline open.
第二条生理盐水静脉通路已开放。
Sepsis panel, UA,\Nurine drug screen, EKG, and CK.
脓毒症检查、尿常规、尿药物筛查、心电图和肌酸激酶检查。
I don't see any\Napparent trauma.
我没有看到任何明显的外伤。
- Pupils reactive.\N- Mr. Scott? Daniel?
- 瞳孔有反应。- Scott 先生？Daniel？
Can you talk to me?
你能和我说话吗？
Post-ictal,\Nbut moving all extremities.
癫痫发作后，但四肢活动正常。
Pulse 137, BP 88/60.
脉搏 137，血压 88/60。
What are you thinking,\NDr. Santos?
你怎么看，桑托斯医生？
Uh, heat stroke,\Nbut consider sepsis or drugs.
嗯，热射病，但要考虑败血症或药物。
Rectal temp is 104.6.
直肠温度 104.6。
All right, let's start\Nwith four ice packs
好的，我们先用四个冰袋
on the groin and axilla.
放在腹股沟和腋窝。
Should we do\Na full body ice bath?
我们应该做全身冰浴吗？
That'll take too long.\NDo you have an Arctic Sun?
那样太费时间了。你们有极地太阳降温仪吗？
Yeah, we do.
有的。
Get pads on the chest,\Nabdomen, and both legs.
在胸部、腹部和两条腿上贴上垫片。
I'll check back in.
我待会儿再来检查。
Ceftazidime is up,\Nand first hemoglobin, 8.2.
头孢他啶已准备好，首次血红蛋白值为 8.2。
8 is pretty low.\NHe must have bled down from 14.
8 相当低。他的血红蛋白一定是从 14 下降的。
Anything you\Nwanna do about that?
你想对此采取什么措施吗？
Um, young, healthy guy.\NWe transfuse at 7.
嗯，年轻、身体健康的家伙。我们在 7 时输血。
Do we?
我们会吗？
We'd be in real trouble\Nif he equilibrates
如果他达到平衡，我们就真的麻烦了
- from acute blood loss.\N- Am I interrupting something?
- 来自急性失血。- 我打扰你们了吗？
- Multiple deep lacerations--\N- Motorboat versus--
- 多处深裂伤-- - 摩托艇对--
Jesus.
天哪。
This looks like some\N"Jurassic Park" shit.
这看起来像某种《侏罗纪公园》的鬼东西。
Is that your official\Nsurgical diagnosis?
这是你的正式手术诊断吗？
He is hemodynamically stable.
他血流动力学稳定。
What else do we know?
我们还知道什么？
Uh, intubated in the field\Ndue to poor tidal volume.
嗯，由于潮气量不足，在现场进行了气管插管。
EFAST was negative\Nfor pneumothorax,
EFAST 检查未发现气胸，
so no need to do a chest tube.
所以无需放置胸管。
And no free fluid\Nin the abdomen,
腹部无游离液体，
good hemostasis\Ninside the wounds.
伤口内止血良好。
Nothing arterial.
没有动脉出血。
At first, he had\Na hemoglobin of 8.2.
起初，他的血红蛋白为 8.2。
We'll follow that closely.
我们会密切监测。
With no active bleeding,\NI wouldn't transfuse just yet.
没有活动性出血，我现在还不会输血。
Dr. Langdon agrees with you.
兰登医生同意你的看法。
Let's get him to CT.
让我们把他送去做 CT 扫描。
Jason Stills, 62,\Nwas gathering the makings
62 岁的杰森·斯蒂尔斯正在准备沙拉的材料时，开始感到头晕和恶心。
of a salad when he started\Nfeeling dizzy and nauseated.
呕吐了一次。
Vomited once.
斯蒂尔斯先生，你感觉怎么样？
How are you feeling,\NMr. Stills?
How are you feeling, Mr. Stills?
Like I'm gonna die.
我快要死了。
Well, you came to the right\Nplace to prevent that.
好吧，你来对地方了，我们可以防止这种情况发生。
Do you mind\Nif I touch your abdomen?
你介意我摸一下你的腹部吗？
- Yeah, sure.\N- Okay.
- 好的，可以。- 好的。
- Does this hurt at all?\N- No.
- 这样疼吗？- 不疼。
He's tachycardic at 124\Nwith a temp of 102.4.
他心动过速，心率 124 次/分，体温 102.4°F。
Hey, Joy,\Nwhat's your suggestion?
嘿，Joy，你有什么建议？
Keep hydrating,\Ncheck electrolytes,
继续补液，检查电解质，
and move him\Nto the cooling room.
把他转移到降温室。
Precisely.
完全同意。
Good luck finding\Na parking spot.
祝你找到停车位。
- North 5.\N- What? No valet?
- 北边 5 号。- 什么？没有代客泊车？
Jada. Hey.
杰达。嘿。
I--I've been looking\Nall over for you.
我——我一直在到处找你。
I just went for a walk.
我只是去散了个步。
I wanted to talk to you,\Nif that's okay.
我想和你谈谈，如果可以的话。
So does Dr. Jefferson.
杰斐逊医生也是这样想的。
It's important that you get\Nto hear what he has to say.
重要的是你要听听他要说的话。
Why?
为什么？
He doesn't want me to go crazy\Nlike my brother?
他不想让我像我哥哥一样疯掉？
Or kill myself like my uncle?
或者像我叔叔一样自杀？
Of course not.
当然不是。
We--we still have no idea\Nwhat caused Jackson's episode.
我们——我们仍然不知道是什么导致了杰克逊的发作。
Episode.
发作。
Right.
对。
Look, I--I know this\Nmust be so scary for you.
听着，我——我知道这对你来说一定很可怕。
And you probably feel\Nbetrayed by your parents.
你可能感到被父母背叛了。
But they had no way\Nof knowing about Jackson.
但他们不可能知道杰克逊的事。
You know, and some families\Njust have a difficult time
你知道，有些家庭就是很难
talking about mental health.
谈论心理健康问题。
Now you can help us\Ntake the first steps
现在你可以帮助我们迈出第一步
to finding out what we can\Ndo to help your brother.
找出我们能做什么来帮助你的哥哥。
Mr. Diaz,\NI have a surprise for you.
迪亚兹先生，我有个惊喜要告诉你。
Oh.
哦。
Sorry.
抱歉。
It's okay.
没关系。
Have you--have you\Nseen my patient?
你有没有——你有没有见过我的病人？
Orlando? Mr. Diaz?
奥兰多？迪亚兹先生？
Room was empty.
房间是空的。
- Seriously?\N- Yeah.
- 认真的吗？- 是的。
What happened to you?
你怎么了？
Oh.
哦。
Bullet grazed my vest.
子弹擦过了我的背心。
You were shot?
你被枪击了？
Shot at.
被射击了。
Geniuses thought today was the\Nday to rob a goods warehouse.
天才们认为今天是抢劫货物仓库的日子。
Didn't think about\Nhow long it would take
没有想到装载电器需要多长时间
to load the appliances.
来装载电器。
They panicked.
他们惊慌失措。
All hell broke loose.
一切都乱套了。
Jesus.
天哪。
Why do you do this?
你为什么要这样做？
My therapist said\NI needed a hobby.
我的治疗师说我需要一个爱好。
Funny.
真有趣。
Shit.
该死。
This--this sucks.
这——这太糟糕了。
- Oh, it's nothing.\N- No.
- 哦，没什么。- 不。
No, don't worry about me.\NI'm fine. Seriously.
不，别担心我。我很好。真的。
No, my patient.
不，我的病人。
He didn't have any insurance,
他没有任何保险，
and he was already\Nin a mountain of medical debt.
而且他已经背负了一大笔医疗债务。
He couldn't afford\Nany of his meds.
他买不起任何药物。
Hmm.
嗯。
What's in the bag?
包里装的是什么？
Insulin, test strips,\Nelectrolyte powder.
胰岛素、测试纸、电解质粉。
I--I got him everything\Nhe needed for home care.
我——我给他准备了居家护理所需的一切。
So Uber it to his house.
那就用优步送到他家。
Is the hospital\Ngonna pay for that?
医院会为此买单吗？
I'll pay for it.
我来付钱。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
What you clearly can't.
你明显做不了的事。
Did you make a chart?
你制作图表了吗？
No.
不行。
This can stay off the books.
这可以不记录在案。
Don't need the paperwork\Nfrom the hospital
不需要医院的文件。
or the police department.
或警察局。
Okay.
好的。
Our little secret.
我们的小秘密。
How's he doing?\NAny more seizures?
他怎么样？还有发作吗？
Nope.
没有。
Temp 102.9.
体温 102.9°F。
Labs back?
化验结果出来了吗？
Mostly signs of dehydration.
主要是脱水的体征。
A tad hypernatremic,\Nmild BUN and creatinine bump.
钠离子稍高，BUN 和肌酐轻度升高。
CK 400 something--\Nnothing worrisome yet.
肌酸激酶 400 多——目前还没什么值得担心的。
Okay, good. Keep cooling.
好的，继续冷却。
- I'll monitor him.\N- Great.
- 我会监测他的情况。- 很好。
That'll give Dr. Santos\Na chance to get caught up.
这样可以给桑托斯医生追上进度的机会。
Your R2 year\Ncan be challenging.
你的 R2 年可能会很有挑战性。
You just have to keep grinding.
你只需要坚持不懈地努力。
What's your dispo plan\Nfor Mr. Scott?
你对斯科特先生的处置计划是什么？
Uh, ICU admission.
呃，入住 ICU。
You should call Neurology\Nto consult.
你应该打电话给神经科进行会诊。
Yeah, done.
是的，已经做了。
Since it was exertional heat\Nillness in a young person,
由于这是一个年轻人的劳累性热病，
the mortality is low.
死亡率很低。
But non-exertional heatstroke\Nin an elderly person,
但是老年人的非劳力性中暑，
- you need to worry.\N- Okay.
- 你需要担心。- 好的。
I'll put in orders\Nfor repeat labs.
我会下单进行重复检查。
Good work in there.
你在那里做得很好。
This 49-year-old woman presents\Nto the emergency department--
这位 49 岁的女性来到急诊科——
Uh, with the chief complaint\Nof right ear pain.
呃，主诉是右耳疼痛。
Hey, Donnie, can you do\Nsomething about that?
嘿，唐尼，你能处理一下吗？
What?
什么？
Seriously?
真的吗？
That--that's not\Ndriving you nuts?
那——那不会让你抓狂吗？
The baby, it won't stop crying.
婴儿一直在哭。
Oh, that?\NIt's music to my ears now.
哦，那个？现在对我来说就像天籁之音。
I think Jesse's the nurse.
我觉得杰西是护士。
Well, can't you--ugh.
好吧，你不能——呃。
Fuck.
该死。
What the hell is going on?
到底发生了什么？
With what?
什么事？
With her.\NCan't you make her stop crying?
关于她。你不能让她停止哭闹吗？
She's been fed and changed.\NShe's cranky from rhinovirus.
她已经吃过奶了，尿布也换过了。她是因为鼻病毒而烦躁。
Isn't there something\Nthat you can do?
你不能做点什么吗？
She's due\Nfor her next Tylenol.
她该吃下一剂泰诺林了。
Give me a minute.\NI'll be right back.
给我一分钟。我马上回来。
Wait, no, no, no,\NI'm not gonna stay here.
等等，不，不，不，我不会留在这里。
What is your problem?
你有什么问题？
This is precisely why\NI didn't go into Pedes.
这正是我没有进入儿科的原因。
Okay.
好的。
Hey, hey.
嘿，嘿。
Hey, little Miss Sunshine.
嘿，小阳光小姐。
Is it time for you\Nto take a little nap?
该是你小睡一会儿的时候了吗？
That would be so fucking nice.
那真他妈的太好了。
Yes, it would.
是的，会的。
I'm starting to understand\Nwhy you got left here.
我开始理解你为什么被留在这里了。
Hey, shh.
嘿，别说话。
What's the word from CT?
来自 CT 的结果怎么样？
Nothing intrathoracic,\Nnothing intra-abdominal.
胸腔内没有异常，腹腔内也没有异常。
Propeller just\Nmissed gutting him.
螺旋桨差点把他的肠子割出来。
- Very fortunate.\N- Okay.
- 非常幸运。- 好的。
Repeat hemoglobin is 8.
血红蛋白复查是 8。
We're holding off\Non transfusing.
我们暂时不输血。
Plan?
计划是什么？
I'll have Mel and Langdon\Nsuture up the lacerations.
我让梅尔和兰登缝合伤口。
Wait, what?\NThat could take days.
等等，什么？那要花好几天。
I--I can't--
我——我不能——
Calm down, Sadness.\NI'm kidding.
冷静，悲伤。我在开玩笑。
This is one for my skilled\Nsurgical residents upstairs,
这个要交给楼上我的高级住院医生。
not you Boy Scout butchers.
不是你们这些童子军屠夫。
Boy, I missed you, Yoyo.
天哪，我想你了，悠悠。
Mm. Can't say the same.
嗯。我可不能这么说。
Okay, let's take up\Nthis art project.
好吧，让我们开始这个艺术项目。
So about before--
那么关于之前的事——
Back to it.
回到正题。
Good talk.
很好的谈话。
How we doing, Princess?
怎么样，公主？
All right.\NA little bloated.
还好。有点胀。
I had one too many hot dogs\Nfrom the truck.
我从卡车上吃了太多热狗。
You meant the board, huh?
你是说董事会啊？
Gus, our incarcerated patient,\Ngot a spot upstairs.
我们的被监禁患者古斯在楼上有了一个床位。
Looking for our unhoused\Npatient, Digby, and, of course,
在寻找我们的无家可归患者迪格比，当然，
we have Whitaker, Donahue,\Nand the med students
我们还有惠特克、多纳休和医学生
on these diversion intakes,\Nbut they just keep coming.
在处理这些转诊入院，但他们源源不断地来。
Yeah, we may need to start\Njust sending people up
是的，我们可能需要开始直接派人上去
and ask for forgiveness\Ninstead of permission.
然后请求原谅而不是事先征求许可。
Hello?
喂？
Oh, okay.
好的。
Yes, I will be right there.
好的，我马上就到。
C-suite wants\Nto see me upstairs.
高管层想在楼上见我。
Ooh, called\Nto the principal's office
哎呀，第一天就被叫到校长办公室
on your first day--\Nnot a good sign.
——不是个好兆头。
- I think I'm a baby whisperer.\N- Hey, great.
- 我觉得我是个哄小孩的高手。- 嘿，太好了。
We'll add Baby Jane Doe\Nto your patient load.
我们会把"婴儿简·多伊"加到你的患者名单里。
Forget I said anything.
当我没说过。
Where are we with\Nyour deaf patient, Harlow?
你那位聋人患者现在怎么样了，哈洛？
Uh, the VRI was a bust, but\Nthe interpreter's on the way.
呃，远程视频翻译没用，但翻译员正在赶来。
Figured I'd just give her\Na head and belly scan
我想我就先给她做头部和腹部扫描
- and go from there.\N- No, wait for the interpreter.
- 然后再看情况。- 不，等翻译员来。
No need to give the patient\Nunnecessary radiation.
没必要让患者接受不必要的辐射。
And your charting?
你的图表怎么样？
Catching up\Nand checking it twice.
正在赶进度，检查两遍。
Good.
很好。
Hey, have you had a chance\Nto speak to Langdon today?
嘿，你今天有机会和兰登谈过话吗？
Uh, no.
呃，没有。
Why? Did he say something?
为什么？他说了什么吗？
No, just curious.
没有，只是好奇。
How is everything at home\Nwith you and Whitaker?
你和惠特克在家里一切都好吗？
He's weirder\Nthan you'd expect.
他比你想象的要奇怪得多。
- Hmm.\N- Yeah.
- 嗯。- 是的。
But I don't see him\Nall that much.
但我不经常见到他。
He spends a lot of time\Nat Amy's.
他花很多时间在艾米那里。
He has a girlfriend?
他有女朋友？
I don't know what to call it.
我不知道该怎么称呼它。
The--the farmer\Nwho got burned last year
那个——去年被烧伤的农民
the day of the mass cas,\Nhis widow, Amy.
大规模伤亡事件那天，他的遗孀，艾米。
Oh, he died?
哦，他死了？
Yeah, he had burns\Non 90% of his body.
是的，他身体 90%的部位都被烧伤了。
His chance of survival\Nwas very slim.
他的生存机会非常渺茫。
Okay, so I'm an optimist.
好吧，我是个乐观主义者。
The sun doesn't always\Ncome out tomorrow, Annie.
太阳不会总是在明天出现，安妮。
Wait, wasn't she pregnant?
等等，她不是怀孕了吗？
No, she was a young orphan.
不，她是个年轻的孤儿。
No, not Annie. Amy.
不，不是安妮。是艾米。
Yes.\NYes, very pregnant and young.
是的。是的，非常年轻，而且怀孕了。
Whitaker is now\Nseeing this Amy?
惠特克现在在和这个艾米交往？
And her baby.
还有她的孩子。
He got really close\Nto the family
他和这个家庭变得非常亲近。
when the husband was dying.
当丈夫快要去世的时候。
He really believed that\Nthe guy would pull through.
他真的相信那家伙会度过难关。
He helped her through\Nthe loss of her husband,
他帮助她度过了失去丈夫的难关，
and then again\Nwhen she had the kid,
后来当她生孩子时又帮了一次，
and now he spends almost\Nevery weekend at the farm.
现在他几乎每个周末都在农场里度过。
Huh.
嗯。
Plus,\Nhe's on the street team,
而且，他在街头小队，
and he just wants\Nto help everybody.
他只是想帮助每个人。
And I just don't wanna see him\Ntaken advantage of, you know?
我只是不想看到他被利用，你懂吗？
He's just\Na fucking Huckleberry.
他就是个该死的傻瓜。
Yeah, but he's our\Nfucking Huckleberry.
是啊，但他是我们他妈的人。
I'll talk to him.
我会和他谈谈。
Hey, your call.
嘿，你说了算。
Strong deflection.\NWell played.
很好的转移话题。玩得不错。
You're the boss.
你是老板。
Or you are until\Nend of shift today.
或者直到今天班次结束。
Still the boss.
仍然是首领。
When you see me in here,\Nstill the boss.
当你在这里看到我时，仍然是首领。
Copy that, Boss.
明白了，首领。
Dr. Robby, can--\Ncan I grab you for a second?
罗比医生，能——能耽误你一秒钟吗？
Yeah. Sure. What's up?
是的。当然。怎么了？
Um, can't you order\Nmy wife to go home?
嗯，你不能命令我妻子回家吗？
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉。
My wife's dying,
我妻子快要死了，
and you're telling me\Nthere's nothing I can do?
你却告诉我我无能为力？
Mr. Hamler, that's not--
哈姆勒先生，那不是——
No, no.
不，不。
There's gotta be something.
一定有什么办法。
Please.
拜托。
It may not seem like much,\Nbut right now,
这看起来可能不算什么，但现在，
you being here for her\Nand respecting her wishes
你在她身边陪伴她，尊重她的意愿
is the best thing that\Nyou can do for her.
对她来说是你能做的最好的事情。
Supporting her and her choices\Nis the most remarkable gift
支持她和她的选择是你在这个时刻能给她的最非凡的礼物
that you can give her\Nat this time.
你能给她的。
And the meds we have her on\Nwill help her pain.
我们给她用的药物会帮助缓解她的疼痛。
And she may get\Nto a point where
她可能会到达一个阶段
she feels well enough\Nto go home.
她感觉好得足以回家了。
Give me one second.
给我一秒钟。
Okay, I'm gonna\Nlet you guys get acquainted.
好的，我让你们彼此认识一下。
I will be right back.
我马上回来。
Oh, oh, oh, excuse me!
哦，哦，哦，对不起！
I--I'm waiting for Dr. Mohan.\NIs she available?
我——我在等莫汉医生。她有空吗？
I will try\Nand find her for you, sir.
我会尽力为你找到她，先生。
Whether you choose to report\Nor not, we're here for you.
无论你是否选择报告，我们都在这里支持你。
Call me any time.
随时给我打电话。
It could be a month\Nor a year from now.
可能是一个月后，也可能是一年后。
I'll follow up with you too.
我也会跟进你的情况。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Thanks.
谢谢。
You've had a pap smear before?
你之前做过宫颈涂片检查吗？
Yeah, every few years.
有的，每隔几年做一次。
Good.
很好。
Same position,\Nbut I'll start with swabs
姿势相同，但我先从外部取样
on the outside,\Nexternal genitalia.
外阴部位。
Then I'll use a speculum\Nto get internal swabs.
然后我会用窥器进行内部取样。
You ready? Okay.
你准备好了吗？好的。
I'll help you get your feet\Nin the stirrups.
我来帮你把脚放进马镫。
Good.
很好。
Okay. All right.
好的。没问题。
Now, slide your bottom down.
现在，把你的臀部往下滑。
Oh. Yeah, a little bit more.
哦。是的，再往下一点。
A little more.
再多一点。
- Sorry. I--I can't.\N- Okay. It's okay.
- 对不起。我--我不能。- 好的。没关系。
We can take a break.\NNo problem.
我们可以休息一下。没问题。
I don't want a break.\NI wanna stop.
我不想休息。我想停止。
Okay.\NIs this about reporting?
好的。这是关于报告的吗？
Because you can do\Nthis collection
因为你现在可以进行这项检查
without a police report\Nfor now.
而不需要警方报告。
And none of it goes in your\Npermanent medical record.
而且这些都不会进入你的永久病历。
I don't wanna do this\Nanymore.
我不想再这样做了。
Tell me why you wanna stop.
告诉我你为什么想停止。
He's my friend.
他是我的朋友。
He knows all my friends.
他认识我所有的朋友。
It was just a dumb--
这只是一个愚蠢的——
he was drunk,\Nhe didn't mean it.
他喝醉了，他不是故意的。
- It didn't mean anything.\N- Okay.
- 这没有什么意义。- 好的。
Okay.
好的。
It's okay. I understand.
没关系。我理解。
I do.
我确实理解。
Ilana, this is a difficult\Nprocess, to say the least.
伊拉娜，说句老实话，这是一个很困难的过程。
Why don't you take a breather\Nand come back?
你为什么不休息一下，然后回来？
And whatever you wanna do,\Nwe'll do.
你想做什么，我们就做什么。
Let's go find\Nthe good snacks.
我们去找点好吃的。
Jesus Christ.
天哪。
Sorry.
抱歉。
Giving new meaning\Nto the nickname Crash, huh?
给绰号"撞车"赋予了新的含义，是吧？
I've been trying to get\Nto the bathroom
我一直在试图进浴室
for over an hour now.
已经超过一个小时了。
Yeah, you and me both,\Nsister.
是啊，我也是，姐妹。
Uh-oh, this can't be good.
哎呀，这不是好兆头。
Who's this?
这是谁？
That is hospital CEO\NTrent Norris.
那是医院首席执行官特伦特·诺里斯。
He's the big boss.
他是大老板。
Hmm. Nice outfit.
嗯。不错的装扮。
Hey, Rockstar.\NGather your staff, please.
嘿，摇滚明星。请集合你的员工。
Sure, anything you\Nwanna tell me first?
当然，你想先告诉我什么吗？
- No.\N- Okay.
- 不。- 好的。
Hey, everybody, can you,\Nuh, gather 'round
嘿，各位，你们能不能聚过来
and listen up\Nfor a moment, please?
听我说一会儿，拜托了？
Can I have your attention,\Neveryone?
各位，能请你们注意一下吗？
Internal disaster at Westbridge
韦斯特布里奇内部灾难
has been identified\Nas a cyberattack.
已被确认为网络攻击。
And now Good Dominion Hospital\Nhas been hit as well.
现在好撒玛利亚医院也遭到了攻击。
Their ambulances are being\Ndiverted over to St. Mary's,
他们的救护车正被转向圣玛丽医院，
but we can expect more walk-ins\Nand Westbridge diversions.
但我们可以预期会有更多自行前往的患者和韦斯特布里奇的转院。
Uh, for how long?
呃，要多久？
We don't know how long.\NIf the ransom is paid--
我们不知道要多久。如果支付赎金的话——
Ransom?
赎金？
Are we next?
我们接下来会不会也遭殃？
Our IT protection system\Nhas blocked thousands
我们的 IT 保护系统在这几个小时内已经阻止了数千次
of intrusion attempts\Nin the hours
入侵尝试
since Westbridge was hit\Nthis morning.
自从今早韦斯特布里奇遭到袭击以来。
But IT believes\Nwe're still vulnerable.
但信息技术部门认为我们仍然很脆弱。
So we're gonna\Npreemptively shut down
所以我们要主动关闭
all the computer systems.
所有的计算机系统。
- Oh, my God.\N- Jesus.
- 天哪。- 天哪。
Patient registration,\Nelectronic health records,
患者登记、电子健康记录、
lab and radiology interfaces,\Nemail, internet.
实验室和放射学接口、电子邮件、互联网。
You didn't wanna\Ntalk to me first?
你不想先和我谈话吗？
You didn't wanna\Nconsult my department?
你不想咨询我的科室吗？
I consulted\Nyour fellow attending.
我咨询了你的同事主治医生。
When are we going down?
我们什么时候下去？
Soon. Very soon.
很快。非常快。
Okay, hey, somebody get\Na picture of the board.
好的，嘿，谁来拍一下这块板子。
Quickly, quickly!\NWe're about to go analog.
快点，快点！我们就要转向模拟了。
- No!\N- Oh, my gosh.
- 不！- 哦，天哪。
- Phones work?\N- They don't work.
- 手机能用吗？- 不能用。
- Oh, my gosh.\N- Did you get the photo?
- 天哪。- 你拍到照片了吗？
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
是的，是的，我拍到了。
This is gonna be fun.
这会很有趣。